Guide to the Charles Henri Ford Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 2004 Acquisition, 1918-2003; 21.95; (27 boxes)
  - Art Files, 1956-2002; Series V; 1.58; (4 boxes)
    - Color and black and white, 2000, undated; 3 (Box 16)
    - Photocopies, CHF, circa 1998; 3 (Box 16)
    - Photographs, 1998-2002; 2 (Box 16)
    - Photocopies of art and CHF, 1996-2000 (Box 16)
    - For scrapbook, 1971-1991 (Box 16)
    - Color artwork on paper, 1996-1999 (Box 17)
      Includes prints, collage, drawings and printed material.
    - Mixed media artwork on paper, circa 1996 (Box 17)
    - Stationery graphic design, photocopies, 1995, undated (Box 17)
    - "Collage material and Xeroxes", 1984 (Box 17)
    - Drawings by William Rand, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Envelopes and notes, 1996-1999 (Box 17)
    - Collages, undated (Box 18)
      Includes collages and photocopies of postcards.
    - Postcards, photocopies, circa 1976 (Box 18)
    - "Happy birthday to CHF!," collage box, 2002 (Box 19)
  - Printed Material, 1942-1977; Series VI; 1.29; (3 boxes)
    - Noh, David, "Fortune and Fame: Artist and Writer Charles Henri Ford says His Life Has Been 'Like a Movie,'" New York Blade News, 1999 May 28 (Box 20)
    - File vol 3 no.3, The Advocate and clippings, 1977, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Printed matter including magazines, articles, and clippings, 1942-1997; 18 (Box 21)
    - Printed matter including magazines, articles, and clippings, 1993-2001; 8 (Box 22)
  - Personal and Financial Papers, 1948-2003; Series VII; 4; (4 boxes)
    - Residence records, Dakota and Paris, 1994-2003; 3 (Box 23)
    - Financial records, 2000-2003; 3 (Box 23)
    - Medical records, 1990-2003; 7 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1969, 1996 (Box 23)
    - "Reserve pictorial," photocopies, undated (Box 23)
    - "Finished business", 1993-2002; 19 (Box 24)
      Includes receipts, correspondence, and bills.
    - "Unfinished business", 1992-1997; 2 (Box 24)
      Art photocopies, correspondence, notes.
    - "Unfinished business", 1948-2003; 25 (Box 25)
      Bank Statements, house rental lease, UBU Artwork, paid bills, pictures, Sotheby's.
    - "Finished business", 1979-1999; 18 (Box 26)
      Correspondence, photographs, bills, receipts, bank statements, notes and clippings
  - Unsorted Papers, 1954-2002; Series VIII; 7.08; (8 boxes)
    - "Permanent file, 1988", 1986-1988 (Box 27)
    - "Permanent file, March 1990", 1959-1990 (Box 27)
    - "Permanent file, 1994", 1993-1995 (Box 27)
    - "Permanent file, 1995", 1987-1997 (Box 27)
    - "Permanent file, 1995", 1991-1996; 2 (Box 27)
    - "To be checked for permanent file, April 1995", 1982-1995 (Box 27)
    - "Archive III", 1983-1999 (Box 27)
    - "Archive III", 1980-1991 (Box 27)
    - "Archive III", 1989-1990 (Box 27)
    - "Archive II, 1996", 1994-1996 (Box 27)
    - "Finished business, Archive II", 1990-1996 (Box 27)
    - "Archive II, for permanent file", 1988-1996 (Box 27)
    - "Archive II, 1996", 1993-1996 (Box 27)
    - "Archive II, reviewed and sealed", 1987-1996 (Box 22)
    - "Archive 1998", 1995-1998; 2 (Box 28)
    - "Permanent file 1999", 1991-1999 (Box 28)
    - "Archive", 1988-2000; 3 (Box 28)
    - "Archive II", 1969-1997 (Box 28)
    - "Archive III", 1989-1996; 2 (Box 28)
    - Envelope, 2001 (Box 28)
    - "Permanent File", 1982-1994 (Box 28)
    - "Dossier, poetry project flyer", undated (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, bills, notes, printed material, clippings, 1985-2000; 2 (Box 28)
    - "Extra prints," correspondence, notes, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, notes, printed material, 1963-2001; 13 (Box 29)
    - Business correspondence, 1968-2002; 4 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1999; 5 (Box 29)
    - Publicity, art and literature announcements, 1998-2003; 3 (Box 29)
    - Writings, 1955, undated (Box 29)
    - Publicity and other papers, 1955-1993 (Box 30)
    - "C.H. Ford Shows", 1980-1998 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence, printed material, 1969-2002; 12 (Box 30)
    - "For Archive II", 1994-1995 (Box 30)
    - "Permanent file", 1994 (Box 31)
    - "Finished business," bills, 1977-1997 (Box 31)
    - "Archive II", 1984-1996; 2 (Box 31)
    - "Archive permanent file", 1999 (Box 31)
    - "Archive III, finished business", 1990-1996 (Box 31)
    - "For permanent file", 1992 (Box 31)
    - Projects, plans, notes, 1989 (Box 31)
    - "Inventory," by Ronnie Burk, 1999 (Box 31)
    - Photographs, 1989 (Box 31)
    - Akehurst Gallery, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Contemporary Art, New York, 2003 (Box 31)
    - "Our Orcas Island," calendar, 2 copies, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Sotheby's, printed material, 1990 (Box 32)
    - Printed material, 1993-2003; 3 (Box 32)
    - Postcards, 1998 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, printed material, 1954-2000; 4 (Box 32)
    - Contact sheets, correspondence, bills, 1994-1999 (Box 32)
    - Gallery announcements, 1982-1992 (Box 32)
    - Dossier: announcements, articles of shows, 1984-1999 (Box 32)
    - Minotaur archives, 1992-1996 (Box 32)
    - UBU Gallery, envelopes, undated; 2 (Box 32)
    - Writings, notes on 4x6 cards, undated (Box 32)
    - Writings, notes on 4x6 cards, undated (Box 33)
    - Checks and check stubs, 1989-2002; 6 (Box 33)
    - Collage and drawing by William Rand, 1995-1996 (Box 34)